In this clip, we'll talk about where to get information on OCD.
One of the quickest and easiest ways is to hop on the Internet in the world wide web.
The one thing you want to do is if you type in OCD for example on one of the search engines, you're going to get pages and pages and pages of information but it's not always the most accurate and correct information.
So, some reliable sources you could go to are webmd.com or you could also go to a site that's dedicated to OCD which is the Obsessive Compulsion Foundation and that website is www.ocfoundation.org.
They have a list of everything from what is OCD to support groups, how to find a doctor in your area things that are going to be really useful and helpful to you.
If going on the Internet is not your thing, you could to talk your primary physician as well.
You could go to a local library and look up some information.
Magazine articles usually medical journals also have some current information.
The most important thing is if you think you might have OCD or if your family member or friend who trying to find out more information about OCD, really get the knowledge get the information find out whichever way you know you can so that you could get your foot in the door.
Once you have the basics, go to someone who knows what they're talking about so a doctor or a therapist someone who could really help you.